instaflex.com 2019-04-01

# Instaflex® Official Site | Instaflex Advanced – Joint Relief | Privacy Policy

This written policy (the "Privacy Policy") is designed to tell you about our privacy practices for the websites, including mobile websites, where it is posted. This includes all of the Adaptive Health company websites (including any pre-sale pages), which are all owned and operated by Adaptive Health LLC ("Adaptive Health", "we", "us" or "our"). When you use any of our websites, we may collect, use and disclose information that you may provide to us through such website or certain related services. This Privacy Policy explains how we handle the information we may hold about you. Please be sure to read this entire Privacy Policy before using, or submitting information, to the website on which this Privacy Policy is posted.

#### **POLICY**

Our policy for all our websites is to respect and protect the privacy of our users. To fulfill this policy, we exercise the precautions set forth in this Privacy Policy to maintain the confidentiality of information provided by you in connection with accessing and using our websites.

We collect your Personal Information as in order to:  
•  Respond to requests and queries you submit to us;  
•  Allow you submit requests for samples and orders for our products through our brand websites;  
•  Create and maintain a unique portal account for you, where available on our website;<  
•  Process payment transactions and send you the products you purchase through our brand websites;  
•  Communicate with you about your purchase orders, or communicate our email newsletter to you, if you make a purchase on our online store or opt-in to receive these communications;  
•  Understand your preferences and tailor offers and services to you based on these preferences; and  
•  Conduct analyses and evaluations to understand consumer trends and usage related to our products in order to improve our websites, services and marketing communications. 

By consenting to our collection, use and disclosure of your Personal Information through your use of our website and services, you will allow us to fulfill the purposes for which we collect your Personal Information, as described above and in this Policy.

#### **YOUR CONSENT**

This Privacy Policy sets forth our current policies and practices with respect to Personal Information of the users of any of our websites. "Personal Information" is any information about an identifiable individual, which includes information such as full name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number and sales delivery, billing and credit card information. By using our websites, you agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy. Whenever you submit information to us through our websites, you consent to the collection, use, and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You can withdraw your consent at any time. However, if you choose to do so, we may not be able to offer you the functionality and services of our websites (for example, if you do not provide your payment information, we cannot process an order for you through our website).

#### **OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN'S PRIVACY**

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. Our websites are not intended for people under the age of majority in their province or territory of residence ("Minors") without the consent from a parent or guardian. We never collect or maintain information on our websites from persons we know to be Minors, and no part of any of our website is designed to attract Minors. We encourage parents to talk to their children about their use of the Internet and the information they disclose to websites.

#### **ACTIVE INFORMATION COLLECTION**

Like many websites, our websites actively collect information from visitors both by asking you specific questions and by permitting you to communicate directly with us via e-mail and/or feedback forms. Some of the information that you submit may be Personal Information.

Some areas of our websites may require you to submit information in order for you to benefit from the specified features we offer (such as newsletter subscriptions, tips/pointers, order processing) or to voluntarily participate in a particular activity (such as sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions). You will be informed at each information collection point what information is required and what information is optional.

#### **DISCLOSURE OF INFORMATION**

We may disclose your Personal Information to contractors, service providers or third party marketers that help us provide services, deliver products or advertisements to you ("Service Providers"). For example, we will disclose your billing information to payment processors to process the transaction, we will disclose your shipping address to fulfillment and shipping contractors to deliver a product to you, and we may disclose your email address to email fulfillment contractors to send you emails from us. These Service Providers are not authorized by us to use or disclose the information we share with them except as necessary to perform the services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. Some Service Providers may be located outside of Canada. You can email us at privacy@adaptivehealth.com if you want to learn more about how our Service Providers use your information.

We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control, in which case we will require these affiliates to honor this Privacy Policy.

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information in certain other situations such as: (a) where we are authorized by law to do so (including to comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas judicial proceeding, court orders or warrants served on us); (b) when you have consented to the disclosure; and (c) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of third parties (including to establish or collect amounts owed to us).

From time to time, we make the email addresses of those who opt-in to receive promotional communications to other reputable organizations whose products or services we think you might find interesting. If you do not want us to share your email address with other companies or organizations, please let us know by contacting us through the contact details provided at the end of this Policy.

If you supply us with your telephone number, you may receive telephone contact (live, automated, pre-recorded or text message) from us, our subsidiaries, affiliates, or agents with information regarding products and services or upcoming events. I understand that my telephone company may impose charges on me for these contacts. If you do not wish to receive such telephone calls, please let us know by emailing us at privacy@adaptivehealth.com.

We engage with third party marketing platforms (such as Google, Yahoo and Facebook) to drive website traffic, raise brand awareness and for product promotion. If you would like to know (1) the categories of Personal Information that we disclosed in the prior calendar year to third parties about you for the purposes of the third party marketing and/or (2) the names and addresses of such third parties, please contact us at privacy@adaptivehealth.com.

We may also share non-Personal Information such as statistical summary data or aggregate analytics data with partners and other third parties (such as Google) at our discretion.

#### **OPT-OUT PROCEDURES**

If you have opted-in to receive our promotional emails, made a purchase through one of our websites, or submitted an inquiry to any of our websites, you may always opt-out of receiving promotional email communications from us. To stop receiving such communications from us, please click the unsubscribe link available in each promotional email or email us at privacy@adaptivehealth.com.

#### **SECURITY OF INFORMATION**

You can be assured that Personal Information collected through our websites is secure and is maintained in a manner consistent with current industry standards. The importance of security for all Personal Information associated with those who access or use our websites and the services they offer is of utmost concern to us. We employ commercially reasonable physical, technological and organization safeguards to protect your Personal Information. Your Personal Information resides on a secure server that only selected Adaptive Health employees and contractors have access to via password. In order to most efficiently serve you, credit card transactions and order fulfillment are handled by established third-party banking, processing agents and distribution institutions. They receive the information needed to verify and authorize your credit card or other payment information and to process and ship your order.

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your Personal Information, you acknowledge that: (a) there are security and privacy limitations of the internet which are beyond our control; (b) the security, integrity, and privacy of any and all information and data exchanged between you and us through our websites cannot be guaranteed; and (c) any such information and data may be viewed or tampered with in transit by a third party. Moreover, where you use passwords, ID numbers, or other special access features on our website(s), it is your responsibility to safeguard them. If you have a user account on any of our websites, you agree to maintain the confidentiality of your account details and notify us immediately of any unauthorized use of your account or any other security breach relating to your account. We are not liable for any loss or damage arising out of your failure to comply with this section.

#### **PASSIVE INFORMATION COLLECTION**

As you navigate through a website, certain information can be passively collected (that is, gathered without your actively providing the information) using various technologies and means, such as Internet Protocol addresses, cookies, Internet tags, and navigational data collection.

Our websites may use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP Address is a number assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider so you can access the Internet. We use your IP address to diagnose problems with our server, report aggregate information, determine the fastest route for your computer to use in connecting to our websites, and administer and improve services to our consumers.

A "cookie" is a bit of information that a website sends to your web browser that helps the site remember information about you and your preferences.

"Session cookies" are temporary bits of information that are erased once you exit your web browser window or otherwise turn your computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on websites and to collect aggregate statistical information. Our websites use session cookies.

"Persistent cookies" are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of your computer and stay there unless you delete the cookie. Persistent cookies store information on your computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information you have previously provided (e.g., username), helping to determine what areas of the website visitors find most valuable, and customizing the website based on your preferences. Our websites use persistent cookies.

"Internet tags" (also known as single-pixel GIFs, clear GIFs, invisible GIFs, and 1-by-1 GIFs) are smaller than cookies and tell the website server information such as the IP address and browser type related to the visitor's computer. Our websites use Internet tags.

"Navigational data" ("log files," "server logs," and "clickstream" data) and "Internet Tags" are used for system management, to improve the content of the site, market research purposes, and to communicate information to visitors. Our websites use navigational data.

You may choose to decline cookies if your browser permits, but doing so may affect your use of our websites and your ability to access certain features or engage in transactions through our websites.

Our websites may also engage in interest-based/online behavioral advertising, which includes ads served to you after you leave our websites, encouraging you to return. These ads are served to you through websites, apps, or emails, based on your shopping habits or other online activities (such as those tracked using the passive tracking technologies described above). We might serve these ads, or third parties may serve these ads about our products or other companies’ products. As a consumer you have the ability to opt-out of having your online behavior recorded and used to serve ads. For more information on how to opt-out, please visit: aboutads.info.

#### **LINKS**

Like many other websites, our websites may contain links to websites of third parties not affiliated with us. These links are provided for your convenience only. This Privacy Policy will not apply to these third-party websites and Adaptive Health is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content on any of these other websites, even where these third-party sites indicate a special relationship or "partnership" with us. We do not disclose personal information to any third party linked sites. The linked sites, however, may collect Personal Information from you when you link to their site. To ensure protection of your privacy, always review the privacy policies of the sites you visit by linking from our websites.

#### **ACCESSING, UPDATING AND CORRECTING YOUR INFORMATION**

You have a right to review any of the information that we hold about you and learn about how we have used it or to whom we have disclosed it by contacting us. Subject to any exceptions prescribed by law, you can access and correct your Personal Information and challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information we have about you. If you have created a user account on a customer portal, you can also view, update or correct your information through your account settings.

However, we may deny access when required or authorized by law. For example, we may deny access when granting access would have an unreasonable impact on other people’s privacy or when necessary to protect our confidential commercial information and the requested information cannot be severed from the balance of the record in which it is contained. If we deny your request for access to, or refuse a request to correct information, we shall explain why.

We keep your information as long as reasonably required to complete our dealings with you (e.g. to complete a transaction with you), or as required by law, whichever is longer. You can also request that we remove your information from our records by emailing us at privacy@adaptivehealth.com. Subject to our requirements for continued retention of your information (i.e., billing, audit, or warranty purposes) or to fulfill our legal obligations, we will make reasonable efforts to honor your request.

#### **CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

This Privacy Policy may change over time. We will post the updated Privacy Policy to our websites or, if we make any substantive changes and you have an account on one or more of our websites, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address associated with your account. If you do not accept the changed version (for example, if you do not approve of a different way that we intend to use Personal Information) you may let us know by letter or e-mail at privacy@adaptivehealth.com. If you do not respond with any objections, we will assume that you consent to changes in the Privacy Policy. Changes will not apply retroactively to Personal Information that was collected before the changes to the Privacy Policy, except as may be required by law.

#### **HOW TO CONTACT US**

If you have any questions, comments, or concerns about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of this site, please contact us via email at privacy@adaptivehealth.com or write to us at:

Adaptive Health LLC  
615 South College St, Suite 1300,   
Charlotte, NC 28202  
USA
